today i will teach you a strategy to recover
your stock stopped
learned this
speaks brother
how are you
I'm making some deliveries
then I'll stop by your beauty store too
tamo together
here is a good example to show it all
oh it's great
thank god
brought a novelty
I can show you
two minutes
I won't take your time
eat brownie
it contains
1 prize
but Golden
get this brownie here
and I'll mix it up in the game that you won't know what it is
found 1 gold bell sticker
gets a T-shirt at Charlie Brown time
e Junior
caraca is there
it's there lie
go buy one now
I just put it in the house
and then the bro already started shopping here
serious
i will win the t-shirt
I'll go there and get it
caraca moleque
did not find
there now it's mine
I'm going to spin
rotate with the week to drill
we are the minority
but in the form of an angel
because life taught me and made me
if it has to be
will be whatever comes
ah I'll take a Chokito
ah I won't take a brownie
because if i bring a brownie
I post a benefit vei
you get scared by the noise too
the noise comes that comes
come to the side
when shouted
passes over
is not marked
closed let's go
marching on that shelf so we can blow up
thank you brother
we don't put the brand to have a price
yes have value
heavy rhythm
strong slow
will look straight at the product
bro game turns
I know I'm talking there
Brownie Junior
came to do here
hide the golden bell in the brownie
where are the brownies
no more brownies
good problem
obligation my brother
stop all flowing
thing happening
guy that too much
but the time has come to open this box
and show you how much I'm making
how much money is coming in
what will be the next steps
Charlie Brown's at Junior
but that only tomorrow
tomorrow is like this
here life is like this
life is everything to me
don't doubt me